[
    {
      "question": "question?",
      "answer": "Yes Signs point to yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "question?",
      "answer": "Don't count on it"
    },
    {
      "question": "question?",
      "answer": "You may rely on it"
    },
    {
      "question": "does my dad not use shirts?",
      "answer": "You may rely on it"
    },
    {
      "question": "bruh?",
      "answer": "It is decidedly so"
    },
    {
      "question": "bruh2?",
      "answer": "Ask again later"
    },
    {
      "question": "bruh?",
      "answer": "It is certain"
    },
    {
      "question": "did that work?",
      "answer": "Ask again later"
    },
    {
      "question": " will my dad stfu?",
      "answer": "As I see it, yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "is that true?",
      "answer": "It is certain"
    },
    {
      "question": " will i pass my tests?",
      "answer": "Yes \u2013 definitely"
    },
    {
      "question": "no",
      "answer": "Most likely"
    },
    {
      "question": "no",
      "answer": "Without a doubt"
    },
    {
      "question": "will this work?",
      "answer": "Without a doubt"
    },
    {
      "question": "is 0 even?",
      "answer": "Most likely"
    },
    {
      "question": "was that fun?",
      "answer": "Most likely"
    },
    {
      "question": "are you working fine?",
      "answer": "You may rely on it"
    },
    {
      "question": "will that ruin something?",
      "answer": "Outlook good"
    },
    {
      "question": "???",
      "answer": "Most likely"
    },
    {
      "question": "ask?",
      "answer": "It is certain"
    },
    {
      "question": "is my dad wrong?",
      "answer": "It is decidedly so"
    },
    {
      "question": "yes",
      "answer": "Concentrate and ask again"
    },
    {
      "question": "will this work?",
      "answer": "Yes \u2013 definitely"
    },
    {
      "question": "corazon is brother of doflamingo?",
      "answer": "Reply hazy try again"
    }
  ]